<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Introduction on Yang's Blog</title><link>http://localhost:1313/</link><description>Recent content in Introduction on Yang's Blog</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Leetcode 242 Valid Anagram</title><link>http://localhost:1313/docs/leetcode/contents/hashmap/242validanagram/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/leetcode/contents/hashmap/242validanagram/</guid><description>Leetcode 242: Valid Anagram # In this post, we will discuss how to solve the popular LeetCode problem: &amp;ldquo;Valid Anagram&amp;rdquo;. This problem requires us to determine if two given strings are anagrams of each other. Two strings are anagrams if they contain the same characters with the same frequencies.
Problem Statement # Given two strings s and t, write a function isAnagram(s string, t string) bool that returns true if t is an anagram of s, and false otherwise.</description></item><item><title>What Happens When You Put a URL in Your Browser?</title><link>http://localhost:1313/docs/cs/content/t2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/cs/content/t2/</guid><description>What Happens When You Put a URL in Your Browser? # Understanding what happens when you type a URL into your browser and hit enter is essential for grasping the basics of web technology. Here’s a detailed step-by-step breakdown of the process.
1. URL Entry and Parsing # Input and Validation: When you enter a URL in the address bar, the browser first validates the URL to ensure it&amp;rsquo;s properly formatted.</description></item><item><title>How to implement set using hashmap in golang?</title><link>http://localhost:1313/docs/golang/content/set/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/golang/content/set/</guid><description>How to Implement Set Using HashMap in Golang # 1. What is a Set? How is Set Different from HashMap? # A set is a data structure that stores a collection of unique elements. Sets do not allow duplicate values and do not maintain any particular order of the elements.
A hashmap is a data structure that stores key-value pairs. Each key in a hashmap is unique, and it maps to a specific value.</description></item><item><title>How to use golang fmt package?</title><link>http://localhost:1313/docs/golang/content/fmt/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/golang/content/fmt/</guid><description>formatting verbs # %s vs %q? Answer: %s prints the string without enclosing it in quotes. %q prints the string enclosed in double quotes, %q can print string, byte slice, runes and int. %v vs %+v vs %#v? Answer: %v: Default format, prints the value as is. For structs, it prints only the field values. %+v: Detailed format, includes field names in structs. %#v: Go-syntax representation, includes type information and can be used to recreate the value in Go code.</description></item><item><title>Quick tutorial on blog web with hugo and netlify</title><link>http://localhost:1313/docs/howtos/content/hugosite/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/howtos/content/hugosite/</guid><description>How to Create a Blog with Hugo and Deploy on Netlify # Creating a blog with Hugo and deploying it on Netlify is a streamlined and efficient process. Hugo is a powerful static site generator that allows for quick and easy website development. Netlify provides seamless deployment and hosting for static sites. Here&amp;rsquo;s a step-by-step guide to get your blog up and running.
Prerequisites # Install Hugo by following the installation guide.</description></item><item><title>Setting Up a New Domain for Your Netlify Website</title><link>http://localhost:1313/docs/howtos/content/domain/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/howtos/content/domain/</guid><description>Setting Up a New Domain for Your Netlify Website # Setting up a custom domain for your Netlify website helps in branding and makes it easier for users to find your site. Here’s a step-by-step guide on how to set up a new domain for your Netlify website.
Step 1: Purchase a Domain # First, you need to purchase a domain from a domain registrar. Some popular domain registrars include:</description></item><item><title/><link>http://localhost:1313/docs/leetcode/contents/linkedlist/23mergeklists/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/leetcode/contents/linkedlist/23mergeklists/</guid><description> leetcode 23: merge k sorted linked list # Caesorum illa tu sentit micat vestes papyriferi #</description></item><item><title/><link>http://localhost:1313/posts/post1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/post1/</guid><description> 11th July # Caesorum illa tu sentit micat vestes papyriferi #</description></item><item><title/><link>http://localhost:1313/posts/post2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/post2/</guid><description> 10th July # Caesorum illa tu sentit micat vestes papyriferi #</description></item><item><title/><link>http://localhost:1313/posts/post3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/post3/</guid><description> 9th July # Caesorum illa tu sentit micat vestes papyriferi #</description></item></channel></rss>